

Nguyen Cong Hien

Mobile developer

Date of birth: Apr, 17, 1997

Gender: Male

Phone: 0961139881

Email: conghienyt97@gmail.com

Address: HCM, Vietnam

OBJECTIVE

To apply all of my experiences during my working process and participating in some contests to become a professional software programmer, and to bring values to the company, help the company complete projects quickly with high quality.

EDUCATION

Oct 2016 - May 2021

University Information Technology

Major: Networking and Communication

WORK EXPERIENCE

June 2018 - jan 2019

Aloapp

Mobile developer Internship

- Maintaining staff management application by android (java))
- Collaborated closely with UX/UI designers to create beautiful,

functional and fast interfaces.

- Collaborated with product team to provide the solution for customer.

Feb 2019 - Sep 2019

Green Market

React native developer

- Create plant management application by React Native, Redux, Redux-
- saga...
- Collaborated closely with UX/UI designers and Dev team to create beautiful, functional and fast interfaces.

,

SKILLS

Language

English,

INTERESTS

I like listening to music, playing game, watching movie...

PROJECTS

UIT Schedule Application

(2019 - 2020)

Customer	UIT student
Description	- This is the app that helps UIT student to search the schedule, infomation of class and grade, deadline convenient, anytime, anywhere from right on your phone.
Team size	2
My position	Front-end Developer
My responsibilities	Analysis and designDevelopmentReview codeOptimize codeBug Fixing
Technologies used	- React Native, redux, redux - saga - Nodejs, mongodb